Guide to the John Burroughs Papers, 1850-1991 (bulk 1860-1921)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
John Burroughs Papers
1850-1991
1860-1921
Burroughs, John, 1837-1921
12.5 cubic feet (68 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Includes 53 original Burroughs journals as well as a typescript of the journals prepared by his granddaughter, Elizabeth Burroughs Kelley, and another typescript prepared by his literary executor, Dr. Clara Barrus. In addition, there are manuscripts, sketch books, scrapbooks and correspondence, including letters to Burroughs from Edith Rickert, Walt Whitman, and others; as well as letters by Burroughs to family, friends, colleagues and readers. The bulk of the correspondence is to and from his wife Ursula and son Julian, but other correspondents include Georgia Avery Kendrick, Clara S. Reed, Minnie and Orlando Rouland, James M. Taylor, Mary W. Whitney, and others. Also included are published and unpublished materials and photographs relating to Burroughs.
Biographical Note
John Burroughs (1837-1921) is one of most important contributors to the canon of American nature writing and was one of the most well-known essayists of his time. He published widely on a variety of subjects in many popular publications, received numerous awards and honorary degrees and was well known to scholars and laypeople alike. However, his popularity waned after his death and only recently has interest in his work been rekindled. His work is of significance to those studying not just natural history, but also ecology, philosophy, poetry, geography, history and many other areas.
Burroughs was born on a dairy farm in Roxbury, New York, in the heart of the Catskill Mountains. As a child he spent much of his spare time reading and writing. He attended various one-room school houses and, for a short time, attended the Hedding Literary Institute in Ashland, New York as well as the Cooperstown Seminary. He left home at seventeen to become a teacher himself, and took posts at rural schools in New York, New Jersey, and Illinois. Throughout, he continued to hone his skills as a writer. Burroughs' earliest journal dates from 1854 when he was 17, but the first form he explored as a public writer (due in part to his love of the work of Samuel Johnson and Ralph Waldo Emerson) was the essay. "Fragments from the Table of an Intellectual Epicure," appeared in the The New York Saturday Press in 1860. His first significant published piece, "Expression" was accepted by Atlantic Monthly later that same year, but because the Atlantic articles were not signed at that point, many, including the editor, mistook the author for Emerson. Soon his work was being published in some of the most popular magazines of the day. He was not, however, able to depend on his writing as a primary source of income for another 25 years.
Burroughs married Ursula North in 1857 and with her encouragement, made the decision to leave teaching to pursue more lucrative work as a clerk for the U.S. Treasury. The couple moved to Washington, D.C. in 1863. While there Burroughs became acquainted with another new arrival, Walt Whitman. The two became fast friends as well as significant influences on each others' work. Burrough's first book, published in 1867, was a defense of the controversial poet: Notes on Walt Whitman as Poet and Person.
In 1873, Burroughs left Washington to return home to New York as a bank examiner. He built his home "Riverby" on a vineyard in West Park, a small town on the Hudson River only 50 miles from his birthplace. In 1881 he constructed his "Bark Study" just off the main house, a quiet retreat (perhaps away from the watchful eye of Mrs. Burroughs, who disapproved of his writing) where he added to his growing body of essays and full length works (see list below). His work garnered substantial popular and critical acclaim, and by 1885 he was able to give up the bank position and fully devote his time to writing and enjoying his land.
Burroughs also enjoyed spending time with his young son, Julian. The couple adopted the child when he was two months old, but Ursula was unaware that her husband had a biological connection to the boy. The child's parentage was somewhat obscure while Burroughs' lived, but the truth was that Julian was John's son. The details eventually came out and there was some family tension, but both parents adored Julian, and the family maintained a close bond.
In 1895, Burroughs built another retreat, this time a mile away from the Riverby house, where it was becoming increasingly difficult to work because of the steady flow of expected (and some unexpected) guests. Still, some visitors were welcome at his new woodland cabin. Family and local friends made the trip out to "Slabsides," including some of his more prominent acquaintances, such as Theodore Roosevelt and Henry Ford. It was also a favorite field trip for Vassar College people, particularly his young friends in the Wake-Robin Club.
Although John Burroughs spent the greater portion of his life within a small radius in New York State, his contact with the world at large was extensive. His travels took him to England, the West Indies, Bermuda, and Hawaii. In the United States he went north to Alaska, south to Georgia, east to New England, and west to California. In 1899 he cruised with the Harriman Expedition to Alaska along with John Muir and others, and in 1903 he traveled with President Roosevelt to Yellowstone National Park.
In 1901, Burroughs met Dr. Clara Barrus, a psychiatrist and admirer of his work. They became friends and eventually she served as his assistant and traveling companion. She also became close with Mrs. Burroughs. In 1914, Barrus moved into a house at Riverby, and when Ursula's health began to fail, the couple stayed with her. Ursula died in 1917 from cancer. Burroughs remained active and continued to write, but he followed Ursula four years later. He died on a train returning from a winter stay in California. Barrus, who became his literary executor, published his last essays in Under the Maples (1921) and The Last Harvest (1922).
Chronology
3 Apr 1837 Born in Roxbury, New York
1854 Began teaching
12 Sep 1857 Married Ursula North
1863 Moved to Washington, D.C., where he began work for the U.S. Treasury
1873 Returned to New York State, took work as a bank receiver
1873 Construction began on Riverby
1878 Julian Burroughs born
1881 Bark Study constructed
1885 Left bank position
1895 Slabsides constructed
1899 Traveled to Alaska with the Harriman Expedition
1901 Met Dr. Clara Barrus
1903 Visited Yellowstone with President Roosevelt
6 Mar 1917 Ursula Burroughs died
29 Mar 1921 Died on a train returning from California
Books by John Burroughs*
1867 Notes on Walt Whitman as Poet and Person
1871 Wake Robin
1875 Winter Sunshine
1875 Squirrels and Other Fur-bearers
1877 Birds and Poets
1879 Locusts and Wild Honey
1881 Pepacton
1885 Fresh Fields
1886 Signs and Seasons
1887 Birds and Bees
1889 Indoor Studies
1894 Riverby
1896 Whitman: A Study
1900 The Light of Day
1902 John James Audubon
1902 Literary Values
1904 Far and Near
1905 Ways of Nature
1906 Bird and Bough
1906 Camping with President Roosevelt
1908 Leaf and Tendril
1912 Time and Change
1913 The Summit of the Years
1915 The Breath of Life
1916 Under the Apple Trees
1919 Field and Study
1920 Accepting the Universe
1921 Under the Maples
1922 The Last Harvest
1922 My Boyhood
*Portions of this listing reprinted with permission from the 2006 Syracuse University Press edition of Signs and Seasons, edited by Jeff Walker.
Scope and Content Note
Vassar's John Burroughs collection consists of journals and some correspondence, as well as published and unpublished materials and photographs relating to the naturalist's personal and professional life. The journals are a significant component of the collection. There are 53 handwritten volumes (circa 3,300 leaves) kept by Burroughs between 13 May 1876, and 4 February 1921. The volumes contain his observations on nature as well as the political, literary, and philosophical commentary, which became the basis for many of his essays. The collection also includes two sets of transcriptions of the journals. The first, annotated and edited by Clara Barrus, covers the journals in the Vassar collection (1876-1921) as well as earlier volumes located in the Berg Collection at the New York Public Library (1854-1876). These transcripts were prepared for the 1928 Barrus publication, The Heart of John Burroughs's Journals. The second transcription was prepared by Elizabeth Burroughs Kelley, granddaughter of John Burroughs and author of several works about him, and includes her handwritten annotations.
Other writings in the collection include manuscript as well has published versions of Burroughs short and full-length works. Much of the manuscript material was annotated in some way by either Clara Barrus or Elizabeth Burroughs Kelley. The same is true for the published versions, and it appears that many items in that series were collected by Elizabeth Burroughs Kelley while doing research on her grandfather.
The correspondence is divided into incoming, outgoing and a miscellaneous series. In both incoming and outgoing, the most frequent correspondents are Burroughs' wife Ursula and his son Julian. Other correspondents include friends, family, neighbors, professional contacts as well as readers of Burroughs' work. Several well-known friends and acquaintances of Burroughs are represented, such as Walt Whitman and Theodore Roosevelt. There are letters to and from artists, such as Timothy Cole, Pietro, and Orlando Rouland, a Burroughs portraitist. There are also several letters showing the connection between Burroughs and members of the Vassar College community, among them: Georgia Avery Kendrick, Clara S. Reed, James Monroe Taylor, and Mary W. Whitney. A series of letters between Fanny Borden, Vassar College Head Librarian, and May Cline, a friend of Burroughs, chronicles the sale of some Burroughs letters to Clara Barrus.
In addition to material created by Burroughs, there is also a variety of materials collected by Kelley and Barrus for their own biographical works on the writer. Series VII and VIII include family and personal documents belonging to Burroughs and the Burroughs family, but also a number of items gathered after Burroughs' death which provide information about his life, his work, the people he knew, and his impact on the world. Included are newspaper clippings, published and unpublished articles, postcards, correspondence and other materials collected as late as 1991.
Access
The repository has digital copies of the 53 Burroughs journals as well as microfilm of the 53 journals and the Barrus and Kelley transcripts. Unless there are extenuating circumstances, readers will be required to use the one of those surrogates. To aid the reader with his/her research, a personal name index has been prepared of those people noted prominently by John Burroughs in his journals.
The rest of the collection is open for research according to the
regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library
without any additional restrictions.
Related Materials
Clara Barrus Papers, Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries.
Although Clara Barrus's transcripts are available in this collection, the earliest original Burroughs journals (1854-1876) are at the New York Public Library in the Walt Whitman Papers.
John Burroughs Collection, Clifton Waller Barrett Library, University of Virginia.
Subject Headings
Names:
Barrus, Clara, 1864-1931; Fisher, G. Clyde, 1878-1949; Kelley, Elizabeth Burroughs; Burroughs, Julian, 1879-; Burroughs, Ursula North; Whitman, Walt, 1819-1892; Muir, John, 1838-1914; Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919; Rickert, Edith, 1871-1938; Kendrick, Georgia Avery, 1848-1922; Reed, Clara S.; Taylor, James Monroe, 1848-1916; Whitney, Mary Watson, 1847-1921
Subjects:
Natural history; Literature; Philosophy; Criticism; Diaries; Authors
Places:
United States--Politics and government
Document Types:
Correspondence; Diaries; Drafts (documents); Galley proofs; Journals (accounts); Maps (documents); Photographs; Printed materials (object genre)
VCL Categories:
Nature and Natural History
Encoding Information
Encoded by Elizabeth Clarke and Laura Streett, 2007. Updated by Emma Gronbeck, November 2023.
Acquisition Information
The bulk of the collection was purchased from Elizabeth Burroughs Kelley in 1982. Other materials were gifts of Elizabeth Burroughs Kelley and others.
Numerous letters, manuscripts, and other materials related to John Burroughs have been purchased and added to the collection, 2002-2019.
The G. Clyde Fisher Papers addition was purchased from James Cummins Bookseller in 2023. [M2023-016]
Three letters and one manuscript excerpt written by Burroughs were purchased from James Cummins Bookseller in 2023 and added to Box 67. [M2023-017]
Other Formats
The journals are also available on microfilm located in Special Collections, and electronically via Hudson River Valley Heritage as well as the Vassar College Digital Library.
Series List
- Series I. Writings: Journals and Notebooks, circa 1858-1921; (Boxes 1-9, 51, 64)
  Series I includes Burroughs' original journals (1876-1921) as well as annotated transcripts by Clara Barrus and Elizabeth Burroughs Kelley. There are also original notebooks, and two sketchbook/scrapbooks. Links to digitized versions of the journals are provided in the container list. Note: not all of the journals include a transcription, so a keyword search of the collection will not include hits from all of the volumes.
- Series II. Writings: Manuscripts, circa 1850-1920; (Boxes 9-11, 51, 64-65)
  Series II consists of typed and handwritten drafts, galley proofs and some transcripts of Burroughs writing. The listing is organized alphabetically by title.
- Series III. Writings: Published Versions, 1859-1920; (Boxes 62, 64-65)
  This series consists of original and photocopied essays and poems from various journals, magazines and newspapers. Although not a complete collection, the series does include a wide range of materials from a variety of publication types. The material is organized chronologically by date of publication.
- Series IV. Correspondence: Outgoing, 1857-1921; (Boxes 11-21, 46, 49-50)
  The bulk of Burroughs' outgoing correspondence is to family members, particularly Julian and Ursula Burroughs. There is also a small collection of letters to others, listed at the end of the series in alphabetical order.
- Series V. Correspondence: Incoming, 1850-1928; (Boxes 21-47, 49-50, 54-55, 64)
  The incoming correspondence is divided into four sections: family, Clara Barrus, non-family organized alphabetically by name, and non-family organized by category.
  There are a number of Julian Burroughs letters in the family section, but there are also letters from Ursula Burroughs, his father Chauncey Burroughs, his brother Hiram, his sister Eden and others.
  The Clara Barrus section includes hundred of letters and postcards dating from 1904-1920 as well as a number of typescripts of letters from 1901-1903.
  Correspondents in the alphabetical non-family section include a large number of friends, neighbors, and professional contacts. Of particular note are the letters from Poultney Bigelow, Clifton Johnson, Ludella Peck, Theodore Roosevelt, and the letter from Walt Whitman.
  The non-family section is organized by category and seems to have been arranged by Elizabeth Burroughs Kelley. It is possible, however, that they were arranged earlier by Clara Barrus and/or Burroughs himself The categories are sometimes broad, sometimes specific, and frequently overlap.
- Series VI. Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1860-1929; (Boxes 47-50, 53, 55)
  The Miscellaneous Correspondence includes letters to Ursula Burroughs, between Ursula and Julian Burroughs, and to and from others.
- Series VII. Biography and Family, 1857-1991; (Boxes 50-52, 55-57, 63-65, and map case)
  The Biography and Family Series includes writings about Burroughs, honors, obituaries, images and artworks depicting Burroughs, items relating to his trips, business and financial documents, and other materials regarding to John Burroughs and his family.
- Series VIII. Research Materials and Library, 1871-1959; (Boxes 50-53, 55-56, 61-62, 64-65)
  The "material by and about others" in this series was collected and arranged largely by Elizabeth Burroughs Kelley. The rest of the series consists of photocopies of title pages of books from Burroughs' library, many of which are now housed in Vassar's Archives and Special Collections Library.
- Series IX. Photographs, 1857-1927; (Boxes 58-60, 63-64)
  The Photographs series consists of formal portraits as well as candids of Burroughs, his family and friends; images of his homes; photos documenting Burroughs' connection to Vassar College; schools he attended or taught at; as well as a number of miscellaneous images.
- Series X. G. Clyde Fisher Papers, 1902-1927; (Boxes ? and 67)
  The G. Clyde Fisher Papers series contains letters to Fisher from John Burroughs, Emily Burroughs, and Clara Barrus, as well as drafts of letters (possibly unsent) from Fisher to Burroughs. Also included are writing drafts from Burroughs and Fisher, as well as photographs of Burroughs and others, including photographs of Burroughs with John Muir and Henry Ford.
Container List
- SERIES I. WRITINGS: JOURNALS AND NOTEBOOKS, circa 1858-1921
  - Original Notebooks and Journals
    - Notebook, 25 Feb 1860 - 16 Nov 1865; (MS, 57 p.) (Folder 1.1)
    - Journal, 13 May 1876 - 13 May 1880; (MS, 87 p.) (Folder 2.1)
    - Journal, 14 May 1880 - 28 Dec 1882; (MS, 68 p.) (Folder 2.2)
    - Journal, 1 Jan 1883 - 28 Oct 1883; (MS, 145 p.) (Folder 2.3)
    - Journal, 9 Nov 1883 - 25 Mar 1884; (MS, 77 p.) (Folder 2.4)
    - Journal, 27 Mar 1884 - 20 Sep 1884; (MS, 90 p.) (Folder 2.5)
    - Journal, 20 Sep 1884 - 30 Mar 1885; (MS, 88 p.) (Folder 2.6)
    - Journal, 1 Apr 1885 - 14 Jan 1886; (MS, 85 p.) (Folder 2.7)
    - Journal, 15 Jan 1886 - 12 Sep 1886; (MS, 61 p.) (Folder 2.8)
    - Journal, 12 Sep 1886 - 1 Jan 1887; (MS, 46 p.) (Folder 2.9)
    - Journal, 11 Jan 1887 - 23 June 1887; (MS, 59 p.) (Folder 2.10)
    - Journal, 24 June 1887 - 21 Oct 1887; (MS, 36 p.) (Folder 2.11)
    - Journal, 21 Oct 1887 - 10 Apr 1888; (MS, 58 p.) (Folder 2.12)
    - Journal, 13 Apr 1888 - 4 Mar 1889; (MS, 65 p.) (Folder 2.13)
    - Journal, 5 Mar 1889 - 1 July 1889; (MS, 32 p.) (Folder 2.14)
    - Journal, 1 July 1889 - 1 July 1890; (MS, 87 p.) (Folder 2.15)
    - Journal, 1 July 1890 - 6 Apr 1891; (MS, 66 p.) (Folder 2.16)
    - Journal, 8 Apr 1891 - 29 Dec 1891; (MS, 63 p.) (Folder 2.17)
    - Journal, 1 Jan 1892 - 8 Aug 1892; (MS, 58 p.) (Folder 3.1)
    - Journal, 9 Aug 1892 - 31 Dec 1892; (MS, 42 p.) (Folder 3.2)
    - Journal, 1 Jan 1893 - 10 May 1893; (MS, 56 p.) (Folder 3.3)
    - Journal, 11 May 1893 - 16 Jan 1894; (MS, 58 p.) (Folder 3.4)
    - Journal, 17 Jan 1894 - 24 July 1894; (MS, 82 p.) (Folder 3.5)
    - Journal, 25 July 1894 - 9 May 1895; (MS, 82 p.) (Folder 3.6)
    - Journal, 10 May 1895 - 27 May 1896; (MS, 93 p.) (Folder 3.7)
    - Journal, 28 May 1896 - 6 Sep 1896; (MS, 29 p.) (Folder 3.8)
    - Journal, 9 Sep 1896 - 27 May 1897; (MS, 68 p.) (Folder 3.9)
    - Journal, 1 June 1897 - 27 Sep 1897; (MS, 21 p.) (Folder 3.10)
    - Journal, 1 Oct 1897 - 4 Apr 1898; (MS, 60 p.) (Folder 3.11)
    - Journal, 4 Apr 1898 - 31 Oct 1898; (MS, 47 p.) (Folder 3.12)
    - Journal, 1 Nov 1898 - 2 Apr 1899; (MS, 42 p.) (Folder 3.13)
    - Journal, 3 Apr 1899 - 15 Feb 1900; (MS, 54 p.) (Folder 3.14)
    - Journal, 16 Feb 1900 - 27 Mar 1901; (MS, 60 p.) (Folder 3.15)
    - Journal, 28 Mar 1901 - 31 Dec 1901; (MS, 60 p.) (Folder 3.16)
    - Journal, 1 Jan 1902 - 31 Dec 1902; (MS, 51 p.) (Folder 3.17)
    - Journal, 1 Jan 1903 - 26 Aug 1903; (MS, 39 p.) (Folder 4.1)
    - Journal, 1 Oct 1903 - 8 May 1905; (MS, 77 p.) (Folder 4.2)
    - Journal, 9 May 1905 - 15 Sep 1906; (MS, 61 p.) (Folder 4.3)
    - Journal, 15 Sep 1906 - 26 June 1907; (MS, 56 p.) (Folder 4.4)
    - Journal, 27 June 1907 - 25 Feb 1908; (MS, 30 p.) (Folder 4.5)
    - Journal, 26 Feb 1908 - 13 June 1909; (MS, 85 p.) (Folder 4.6)
    - Journal, 17 July 1909 - 22 Mar 1910; (MS, 50 p.) (Folder 4.7)
    - Journal, 23 Mar 1910 - 11 Apr 1911; (MS, 77 p.) (Folder 4.8)
    - Journal, 14 Apr 1911 - 24 Mar 1912; (MS, 67 p.) (Folder 4.9)
    - Journal, 25 Mar 1912 - 4 Nov 1913; (MS, 89 p.) (Folder 4.10)
    - Journal, 10 Nov 1913 - June 1915; (MS, 80 p.) (Folder 4.11)
    - Journal, 1 July 1915 - 5 May 1916; (MS, 54 p.) (Folder 4.12)
    - Journal, 8 May 1916 - 27 Nov 1916; (MS, 68 p.) (Folder 4.13)
    - Journal, 27 Nov 1916 - 23 Mar 1917; (MS, 45 p.) (Folder 4.14)
    - Journal, 24 Mar 1917 - 6 Dec 1917; (MS, 84 p.) (Folder 4.15)
    - Journal, 5 Dec 1917 - 31 Oct 1918; (MS, 63 p.) (Folder 4.16)
    - Journal, 1 Nov 1918 - 28 Mar 1919; (MS, 48 p.) (Folder 4.17)
    - Journal, 29 Mar 1919 - 21 Mar 1920; (MS, 67 p.) (Folder 4.18)
    - Journal, 22 Mar 1920 - 4 Feb 1921; (MS, 66 p.) (Folder 4.19)
    - Notebook - tracks berry sales, includes some commentary, 1878 (Folder 51.3)
    - Fragment of journal kept during a European trip, July-Sep, [no year] (Folder 51.4)
  - Edited Transcript of the Journals by Dr. Clara Barrus
    - Explanatory note and preliminary leaves of the manuscript; Entries for 1854-1859, pp. i-xiv, 1-40, (TS, 54 p.) (Folder 5.1)
    - Entries for 1859, pp. 41-74, (TS, 36 p.) (Folder 5.2)
    - Entries for 1859-1868, pp. 75-128, (TS, 55 p.) (Folder 5.3)
    - Entries for 1865-1866, pp. 129-172a, (TS, 49 p.) (Folder 5.4)
    - Entries for 1866-1875, pp. 173-208 [pp. 173-180 are also marked 159A-159I], (TS, 43 p.) (Folder 5.5)
    - Entries for 28 Jan 1876 - 23 Dec 1878, pp. 209-252, (TS, 46 p.) (Folder 5.6)
    - Entries for 10 Jan 1879 - 26 Apr 1882, pp. 253-295, (TS, 43 p.) (Folder 5.7)
    - Entries for 28 Apr 28, 1882 - 25 Aug 1883, pp. 296-342, (TS, 51 p.) (Folder 5.8)
    - Entries for 30 Aug 1883 - 20 Aug 1884, pp. 343-387, (TS, 46 p.) (Folder 5.9)
    - Entries for 1 Sep 1884 - 14 Jan 1886, pp. 388-434, (TS, 49 p.) (Folder 5.10)
    - Entries for 15 Jan 1886 - 31 Oct 1887, pp. 435-480, (TS, 49 p.) (Folder 6.1)
    - Entries for 1 Nov 1887 - 2 Apr 1890, pp. 481-531, (TS, 51 p.) (Folder 6.2)
    - Entries for 3 Apr 1890 - 27 May 1892, pp. 531a-580, (TS, 51 p.) (Folder 6.3)
    - Entries for 30 May 1892 - 19 Mar 1895, pp. 581-631, (TS, 52 p.) (Folder 6.4)
    - Entries for 21 Mar 1895 - 22 Mar 1898, pp. 632-684, (TS, 53 p.) (Folder 6.5)
    - Entries for 25 Mar 1898 - 31 Dec 1900, pp. 685-735, (TS, 53 p.) (Folder 6.6)
    - Entries for 1 Jan 1901 - 27 June 1904, pp. 736-785, (TS, 51 p.) (Folder 6.7)
    - Entries for 28 June 1904 - 18 Dec 1908, pp. 786-837, (TS, 52 p.) (Folder 6.8)
    - Entries for 19 Dec 1908 - 23 June 1911, pp. 838-884, (TS, 50 p.) (Folder 6.9)
    - Entries for 24 June 1911 - 23 May 1914, pp. 885-937, (TS, 50 p.) (Folder 6.10)
    - Entries for 24 May 1914 - 19 Dec 1916, pp. 938-986, (TS, 50 p.) (Folder 7.1)
    - Entries for 22 Dec 1916 - 4 Oct 1918, pp. 987-1033, (TS, 50 p.) (Folder 7.2)
    - Entries for 9 Oct 1918 - 20 Mar 1920, pp. 1034-1077, (TS, 51 p.) (Folder 7.3)
    - Entries for 22 Mar 1920 - 4 Feb 1921, pp. 1078-1102, (TS, 32 p.) (Folder 7.4)
  - Transcript of the Journals, with Annotations by Elizabeth Burroughs Kelley
    - Entries for 28 Jan 1876 - 10 Mar 1879, pp. 209-255, (TS, 48 p.) (Folder 7.5)
    - Entries for 11 Mar 1879 - 8 Oct 1882, pp. 256-309, (TS, 54 p.) (Folder 7.6)
    - Entries for 13 Oct 1882 - 13 Mar 1884, pp. 310-367, (TS, 58 p.) (Folder 7.7)
    - Entries for 16 Mar 1884 - 13 Apr 1885, pp. 368-416, (TS, 50 p.) (Folder 7.8)
    - Entries for 14 Apr 1885 - 1 May 1887, pp. 417-468, (TS, 52 p.) (Folder 7.9)